=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 7=
He got here this morning.
No way he just got here.
He still has his wine out.
You have to
hand it to our boss.
Then, where is Ms. Lin?
- Ms. Lin.
Look at him.
- See that?
- Time for work.
Morning, Ms. Lin.
- Ms. Lin.
- Morning, Ms. Lin.
- Back to work.
Why are you sleeping here?
Why can't I sleep here?
I bought this sofa, you know.
What's up?
Did you sleep? Did you go home?
Go home and get some rest.
She talked with me all night.
I was working late,
and He Han came up...
No need to explain.
Just go. I need to get to work.
I can't leave, Lin Zhanqiao.
Listen to me.
Do me a favor.
What is it?
Mimi has me cornered at my hotel.
Come back with me.
If she sees us together,
she'll finally
leave me alone.
You created this mess,
so clean it up yourself.
I'm busy.
So you'll leave me hanging,
Lin Zhanqiao?
I was never loyal.
Zhangzhu,
how about you come with me?
Not a chance.
Go home and rest up.
Take the morning off.
Get some sleep.
Thanks, Ms. Lin.
Coffee.
No thanks.
What?
Need a private chat?
Do you remember the lore book
for "Drunk Old Friend"?
Of course.
I threw it away.
If you still have it,
give it back.
Have you forgotten?
Someone plagiarized the Guazhou section,
which is why we threw it away.
Why?
Is Gu Yan writing it now?
He can't go through Guazhou.
Take Zhichi Gorge instead.
That's none of your business.
The copyright for all project materials
belongs to Chenxing.
If you still have it,
you should return it.
Of course, you could say
you lost it.
Then, forget it.
Still insisting on Guazhou?
Fine. Very ambitious.
I'll go back and look.
If I find it, it's yours.
It's useless to me anyway.
Your dad's birthday is coming up.
How are you celebrating?
Is your mom going?
You're resuming updates soon.
Are you ready?
What if you lose
to Gu Yan
or Hong Qigong
on the charts?
I'll contact your dad.
See you then.
Is the breakup with Mimi sorted?
Don't be late.
See? I didn't lie.
This apartment
is the best unit in the building.
The natural light,
the decor, and the appliances
are all top-tier.
Your rent offer is way too low.
It's hard to rent places out now.
If you use an agent,
they'll charge you a fee.
If you love this building so much,
how about I show you
the smaller unit next door?
It's also for rent.
It's a one-bedroom?
Too small.
You live alone.
How much space do you need?
Is there someone else?
Then, I can't rent to you.
Even though
I'm over you,
if another man
stays in my apartment,
well...
I'm paying rent.
You're paying too little.
You taking advantage of me is one thing.
But another man, too?
No way.
It's settled.
15,000 yuan a month.
I'll live alone.
If there's someone else?
10,000 yuan per person.
Deal.
Hello.
Dai Shan.
I told him early on.
A harem plot
in this chapter is dangerous.
He didn't listen.
Look at him now.
His stats are tanking,
and fans are angry.
He comes to drink every day.
He calls me when he's drunk,
and vents for three hours.
Says he needs to talk.
I'm not an editor anymore.
I'm his personal relationship guru.
I think it's nice.
He talks to you.
I need to take this.
(Ladies,)
(stubbornly chasing a jerk)
(means you lack self-respect.)
(Sometimes,)
(we can't help but reach out.)
(Because we still love him.)
(Because we haven't woken up.)
(But after all the begging,)
(pleading, and crying,)
(in the end...)
(He already has someone new.)
(And it's someone he met at work.)
(They've been together a while.)
(And they never really ended it.)
(Who is this person?)
(I'll reveal it in my novel.)
Met through work,
and already together?
It has to be Ms. Lin.
Did He Han
and Ms. Lin stay together?
Didn't they break up?
Maybe they got back together.
They are soulmates.
The kind that are intertwined.
You wouldn't get it.
Do you believe everything you hear?
What soul sees us as partners?
Are you the love expert?
Tell your authors to intertwine
their male and female leads, then.
Stop letting them
stare longingly from afar.
No one will read that!
In a rush?
Are you...
I'm turning the place upside down.
I can't find it.
I'm not talking about that.
I told you,
don't drag me into Mimi's mess.
What does she want?
True stories?
Live updates?
Old loves and new flames?
Listen up!
If she dares to write about me,
or makes up lies
about us reconciling,
to get clicks and reads,
I can sue her!
And I'll sue you, too!
I didn't provoke her.
We already broke up.
She always twists my words.
Lin Zhanqiao, listen.
The truth speaks for itself.
Whatever she wants to say,
just let her say it.
If this stops you
from getting a new boyfriend,
let me know.
I'll talk to him for you.
I'm done talking to you!
It's making it worse!
Zhangzhu.
You gave her time off, so she went home.
Do me a favor.
Contact Dingqi.
Tell them
to make Mimi delete that smear video.
Right, Ms. Lin.
Good news.
Ms. Wu from Zhiyuan Investment
wants to see you this afternoon.
Tell her
I'll see her at 2 PM.
Also,
tell Gu Yan
not to come today.
Okay.
Sir.
You can't go in.
Sir!
Please wait a moment.
You can't come in.
Ms. Lin.
Zhangzhu's father is here to see you.
You're Zhangzhu's boss?
Lin Zhanqiao,
head of Chenxing.
You owe me an apology.
Who is he?
I don't know.
I think it's
Zhangzhu's dad.
For what?
How old are you?
You're clearly not a child.
My daughter is only twenty-two.
You need to apologize
for filling her head
with terrible ideas.
What terrible ideas did I teach her?
Encouraging her
not to call my new wife Mom.
That she has the right to accept
this new mother,
and the right to reject her.
"Our home
is her father's home."
"It isn't her home."
"Live elsewhere"
"under another's roof."
"She deserves
a real home of her own."
What kind of boss are you?
Aren't you overstepping?
She comes here to work,
not to be brainwashed.
You seem educated.
You should know better than me,
that the most important quality
is filial piety.
Right?
First of all,
I never said that to Zhangzhu.
If not you, then who?
Are there other bosses?
It's this place.
You're ruining my daughter.
Second,
I had never met you before.
And I just found out
your new wife would be
Zhangzhu's new mother.
I would've said the same
had she asked me.
I don't see anything wrong with it.
Zhangzhu is twenty-two.
She's not twelve.
She is your daughter.
But she is also
an independent adult.
She deserves your respect.
Let me tell you.
I do not allow my daughter
to keep working here.
Then please ask
your daughter's opinion.
And respect her decision.
I can't talk to you.
Ms. Liu.
It's Ms. Lin.
Let's go.
What?
Was calling not personal enough?
You had to come in person?
Let me ask you.
What did you tell Zhangzhu?
Her dad just came here
and chewed me out!
He went to your office
and chewed you out?
Doesn't that prove I was right?
Her dad is the problem.
Zhangzhu is my assistant.
I finally found
a competent assistant.
Your late-night talk with her
could've made her quit!
Can you get me a new one, then?
Before you speak,
use your brain
and think of the consequences!
Hold on.
Who could've seen this coming?
Right?
You know what I said.
So you must agree with me.
You probably even admire me.
You're pretending to be mad.
I can tell.
But I have to say,
Zhangzhu is a
smart girl who knows what's right.
Is she back at the office?
She's my assistant.
If anything comes up,
I can handle it.
Why don't you
go talk to her dad?
Stop running your mouth
and blaming me, okay?
Yes, you're not busy.
You can ride your bike.
But I can't. I have to work!
I'm working, too.
I'm looking for the lore book.
If you have time,
we can sit down and review it.
We can probably figure it out.
I'm busy.
It's expensive.
Your boss is here.
Sorry, Ms. Lin.
Give me a second.
It's fine.
I'm heading back to the office.
I'll contact you.
Just give me five minutes!
No rush.
Finish today's work first.
We can deal
with the Guazhou arc later.
I'm leaving.
What's wrong?
Ms. Lin shouldn't see us like this.
Isn't this normal?
Mei, where are you?
Didn't you know Gu Yan had a girlfriend?
I knew.
Then, why are you freaking out?
I wasn't prepared for it.
I used to visit He Han like this.
And I never ran into
such an awkward situation.
He Han was your boyfriend.
Gu Yan isn't.
Back then, He Han and I
weren't even dating.
We just met,
and worked together.
Nothing like this ever happened.
That's because he's experienced,
and hid it from you.
Mimi just dropped a bombshell.
She said He Han is two-timing.
When did this happen?
"Wide Awake"
updated this morning.
(Wide Awake)
Am I that kind of person?
We already broke up.
Why would I go back
to fight a woman like Mimi over He Han?
Even I wouldn't believe it if I said it.
Another update.
The Jerk's Romance
with His Older Manager.
(Chapter 7: The Jerk's Romance
with His Older Manager)
(Ladies,)
(the worst part isn't being cheated on.)
(It's realizing I was the other woman.)
(He was with his manager all along.)
(I was fooled for so long.)
(How could I be so stupid?)
(They are two of a kind.)
I could hear you laughing
from the elevator.
Is it that funny?
How is this not funny?
Lin Zhanqiao thought it was her.
She even went to Dingqi,
demanding they delete the video.
I can just imagine the look on her face.
I never thought
I'd fail so miserably
in love.
Oh my goodness.
What is all this?
Did you do this?
Would she have left otherwise?
You mean you're He Han's new flame?
After he and Lin Zhanqiao broke up,
we got together.
I don't believe it.
You look much older than him.
Listen to me.
This will really help
with tonight's click rates.
What were you going to write?
That his new flame
is another female author?
They could sue you for slander.
Lin Zhanqiao...
Is it original
to rekindle an old flame?
No.
Plus, what chapter
are you even on?
If they get back together now,
what's left to write?
That's why
you have to use my idea.
It perfectly satisfies
their craving for gossip.
Plus,
the jerk persona
is taken to the next level.
I'm serious.
This is pure genius.
Never mind Mimi.
Even I'm in awe.
Come on. Sit down.
Absolutely brilliant.
A total masterpiece.
She just wanted
to milk you for content.
So I taught her a lesson.
I can never repay you.
Except with my body.
I may flirt
with young girls.
But it means nothing.
I actually value brains.
With a mind like yours,
age is just a number.
I'm not interested in younger men.
I only want your drafts.
Save your brains and everything else
for the other girls.
You really won't consider it?
You like older men.
How old is Mr. Fan?
He's got to be eighty-five.
Isn't that too old?
Twenty-year-olds
probably think you're old, too.
But you don't mind, do you?
Fair point.
I should hit the gym more.
Catch.
Take it for a spin.
Thanks, boss.
Don't mention it.
Being generous to my girlfriend
only makes me look good.
Tell me,
is it true about him and Dai Shan?
Find it hard to believe?
You'd rather believe
he's with Mimi or Jia Jia?
Dai Shan
is Mr. Fan's ex-wife.
So what?
Can you take your calls outside?
Taking it here
disturbs everyone else.
You think you're the sun?
That we all revolve around you?
You only care about dating.
Does dating make us money?
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and fix it.
Send out a notice.
Editors and authors cannot date.
Otherwise, how can they
stay objective?
Understood, Mr. Fan.
I hate people
who can't separate work and life.
What is it, Fan?
Are you serious about He Han?
He is my top author.
Even so, I don't want him
to live in my apartment.
I hope
you remember your promise to me.
Fine. Don't worry.
I won't let him come over.
"Shattered Six States" is relaunching.
You promised me prime promotion spots.
You'd better remember your promise, too.
I'm driving. Bye.
I think this judge is great.
Is it true, Ms. Lin?
How would I know if it's true?
Go ask He Han yourself.
You have his number.
I meant Guazhou.
Are we really writing them into Guazhou?
Isn't it drafted and uploaded?
On Monday,
"Drunk Old Friend" enters Guazhou.
He Han's
"Shattered Six States" relaunches.
If we make such huge plot changes now,
we could lose readers.
I'm confident.
Once it's published,
there's no turning back.
If the readers hate it,
we're done for.
I sent it to the website.
Stop asking.
Prepare the next batch
of lore for He Han.
For Gu Yan.
(He Han)
Hello?
Flattering yourself, aren't you?
Regret blowing up at me earlier,
don't you?
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
It's fine.
I'll be the bigger person.
It's all water under the bridge.
But I'm calling to ask,
how is Zhangzhu?
Did her dad
really stop her from working?
If so, I need to talk to him.
She's my number one fan.
I'm responsible for her.
I haven't contacted her.
Even if something happened,
it's not your place to see him.
I'm her boss. I'll handle it.
Fine, you handle it.
If you can't, come to me.
By the way, I'll drop by tomorrow.
See you.
♪I watch stars in my eyes♪
♪Slowly tripped away♪
♪I don't know it inside last night♪
♪Cause I never see you again♪
♪I'm waking up
to silence in the morning♪
♪Heal, can I heal?♪
♪All I want is nothing but♪
♪Better see your face someday♪
♪All I wish that you
could hear my voice♪
♪And know that I won't forget you♪
♪Never forget you♪
What is this?
About today...
I'm sorry.
I told San Mei
not to come anymore.
From now on, that's my workspace.
You can check on me anytime.
I shouldn't make you feel uncomfortable.
Put this back and keep it safe.
Who locks their girlfriend
out of a room?
You weren't replying to my messages.
I thought you were mad.
I was in a meeting with Zhiyuan.
Right.
I have good news.
Zhiyuan agreed to invest.
But I was also mad.
Not because
San Mei was in your room.
That's your business.
It's because you game all night.
You write all day,
with zero sleep.
If you keep this up,
it'll ruin your health.
We used to make money gaming.
If I quit,
they'll lose a lot of income.
I can't just abandon them,
just because I can make money
writing online now.
But you can't let loyalty
hold you back like this.
What's wrong?
I think Wang Hai and I are breaking up.
No way.
He's afraid of Lin Zhanqiao.
He took the keys back from me
so Lin Zhanqiao wouldn't be upset.
You know, you're overthinking it.
Lin Zhanqiao is his boss.
Of course he's afraid.
That's not what I mean.
Stop playing dumb.
(Esports Internet Cafe, Arcades)
Let me tell you,
even if he's aiming out of his league,
would Lin Zhanqiao ever go for him?
He's a top author now.
So what?
Lin Zhanqiao just uses him for money.
She'd use anyone.
When it's all over,
won't he just be
a lousy admin here again?
He gets it.
We're at the bottom.
They're at the top.
Two different worlds.
He goes up for a spin,
broadens his horizons,
and comes back to brag to us.
That's enough.
Back to reality.
If he really wants to be their equal,
he should build
good karma in this life,
and hope for a better next life.
He might not think that way.
Slap him twice and he will.
Boss, instant noodles with sausage.
Coming.
It's PC 16.
Ms. Zhou.
Why don't we
add each other on WeChat?
If you want to add Ms. Zhou,
you need Mr. Bei's permission.
Really?
I wouldn't dare make decisions for her.
Come on, let's add each other.
Alright. Mr. Bei,
we're taking off.
- Alright, bye.
- Bye.
- See you.
Bye.
Ms. Zhou.
If you have time tomorrow morning,
let's meet with your mother.
First,
we need to check
the property rights of her current home.
Then,
we need to understand her intent.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Bei.
To Three on the Bund.
Okay.
You lucked out today.
What year is this?
It's an 18-year Dalmore.
18 years?
No wonder.
No wonder it's strong.
Really? I'm a bit dizzy, too.
But you aren't flushed. You can drink.
I will be there soon.
You did drink a lot.
It's alright.
Excuse me.
I need a word with Ling Yikai.
Why are you here?
Wait for me.
Okay.
Why the bad mood?
Who is she?
Talking business.
That involves me, too.
Let's talk together.
Listen,
Zhiyuan already
gave the money to Chenxing.
We didn't get a dime, understand?
So?
You came to drown
your sorrows and pick up girls?
If the girl brings in investments,
why wouldn't I?
Stop hovering over me.
Go find some money.
This girl you mentioned
will invest
seven million yuan in us this month.
Can you do that?
Can you?
I'm not playing around.
You said
we'd exchange resources.
You said you're capable
of bringing me huge profits.
If you deliver,
I'll stay by your side.
If you can't,
don't talk to me about feelings.
It means you have no respect
for the rules of our game.
How much did she bring in a month?
Seven million.
I'll get it for you.
In one month?
Here.
What?
Take a photo.
For our seven million.
Come.
(Zhao Lanxin: Party on the Bund)
(Zhiyuan Venture Capital Allocation,
Chenxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.)
Hello?
I got the ginseng you couriered.
You're not coming over?
I'm not going back today.
I'm seeing my mom tomorrow.
Why are you seeing her?
Mr. Bei and I are checking out
her house to figure out
how to talk to my dad.
If all else fails,
we'll take legal action.
Does Mr. Bei know how you act
in front of your mom?
No.
But he knows
she's a very traditional woman.
And your nail polish?
Removing it now.
And your hair?
I'll straighten it tomorrow morning.
Don't worry.
Shoes, bags, and clothes...
It's all prepared.
Armed to the teeth.
Wish your dad a happy birthday.
Tell him to slice the ginseng for tea.
I'll thank you on his behalf.
By the way,
I have good news.
Looks like I'll secure
Zhiyuan's investment.
This finally solves
my immediate problem.
I acted so confidently
at the office every day.
But deep down, I knew
I was almost completely broke.
Thank you.
Alright.
We both have battles tomorrow.
Get some rest.
You too. Bye.
(Property Management Fee Notice)
(Received. Will pay within a month.)
You're not mistaken. It's me.
Let's go.
You suddenly got so serious.
Zhang Yousen and I
aren't quite used to it.
Yeah.
It's a huge change.
May I know
why you dressed like this
to see your mom?
My mom has always
hated flashy women the most.
It's kind of like PTSD.
So I can never let her know
I wear heels and lipstick,
and floral dresses.
But your style...
I mean your actual style.
Does your mom know?
No.
She never let me wear skirts
or leather shoes when I was young.
So when I grew up,
all my money
went to clothes and makeup.
Call it rebellion.
What if
she finds out?
She'll go crazy.
Looks like today's legal consult
just got harder.
Here. Thanks.
Slippers are here.
Thanks.
Thank you.
We're family.
If we can avoid a lawsuit,
we should.
Best to keep
outsiders out of it.
He divorced you over a decade ago.
We aren't family.
Ms. Zhou told me
her father
wants to sell this house,
and split the proceeds equally.
I don't want to sell.
The other woman wants his money.
So he's targeting this house.
Mr. Bei,
if you can make him see
she's just using him,
and he wants to move back temporarily,
I'm open to it.
Mom.
He's not coming back.
Mr. Bei,
you can tell
my daughter and I
are decent people.
She's never
even dated.
How could we possibly
meet with that woman?
I don't want her
to pollute my daughter's mind.
Please meet her
on our behalf.
Tell her
that ruining a marriage
and coveting property
are highly immoral.
There will be serious consequences.
Right?
Mr. Zhang,
staring at my daughter like that
seems a bit rude.
No.
I'm sorry.
I just thought of some related cases.
Right.
You're wearing nail polish.
I got a marker on it.
Don't lie to me.
I can tell.
What is it, some kind of gel?
It won't even scratch off.
Mom.
A colleague bought it
and tested the color on me.
Which colleague?
Tell me.
I need a word with her.
She's a bad influence on you.
We must
always be
upright people.
Especially girls.
A well-raised girl
shouldn't focus
on things like this.
Right?
This is
unintentionally
tempting to men.
You could even call it seduction.
Right, Mr. Bei?
But I wiped it off right after testing.
See?
My other fingers are clean.
Could you two please wait outside?
Tell me.
Did you secretly
paint your toenails, too?
Ms. Zhou.
Later on,
you need to visit our firm.
We need to talk.
Then,
we have to meet your father.
Please wait outside first.
Take off your shoes.
You do it,
or I'll do it for you.
(Changchun Apartments)
I could get you the shoes.
Forget it.
Where's Mr. Bei?
In the car.
Careful.
Sorry.
You shouldn't have seen that.
I'm a lawyer.
Believe me,
I've seen all kinds of clients.
No, I just never thought
this would happen to you.
Shows you're still young.
You have a lot to learn from Mr. Bei.
Let's get you home.
Okay.
Growing up like that,
and still becoming
the Zhou Mei we know,
is truly remarkable.
My mom was a top student.
A prodigy.
An apple of everyone's eyes.
When my dad married her,
he said he loved her brilliant mind.
But when they divorced,
he said she was boring.
So your dad
found a new wife.
A mistress.
Not a new wife.
My mom knew where she lived.
She took me there with her.
(Year 2004)
She acted just like
what you saw earlier.
And...
What about you?
Me?
You wouldn't believe it.
I was mesmerized.
Every inch of her house
was beautiful.
Of course, I hated her.
She stole my dad.
She caused us
so much pain and humiliation.
But at the same time,
I really loved her clothes.
Her jewelry.
Even
the smell of her house.
♪My heart is beating still♪
♪Sometimes I feel alone♪
♪But love should not be frail♪
♪Is there a spell♪
♪that lies inside my head♪
♪Stand naked and haunted♪
♪If there's a way♪
♪To save me from the blue days♪
♪I guess♪
♪It's rising from my silence♪
♪I'm nothing but the one♪
♪Who paints the blue sky♪
♪With all of my tears♪
♪And past pain♪
♪I'd still try♪
♪Please stay with me♪
♪I could've held you in my arms♪
♪When I said love♪
♪Hurts somehow♪
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪